I promise, I will make your wish come true.
Even if it means hurting someone else.
Even if it means hurting myself.
But when your dream becomes reality,
there's something I must ask in return.
Please, no matter what, smile for me.
Fast.
At least for me.
We are if you are still alive.
実は人絵に カードの裏を持て 解けない
目めくりめくるなく 目まぐるしいステージで
その絡まった感情 満足いくまで何回も
壊してしまう
運命に手招きされ彷徨う明日は
何を選んで何を手放し一つになればいいんだろう
馴染った手札を晒く余裕なんてないよ
乾いた後悔の海を飲み越す君は
限られた言葉でいつしかの笑顔を許してほしいんだろう
現実を忘れたって構わないよ
だから今も知らないでいたいな
For real? Iona plays Wecross too?
Yeah, so? Wecross is fun!
Even I bought a starter deck.
I thought it was a guy thing.
But whatever, I guess.
Whatever, I guess.
Hello, Ruko. Welcome home.
Hey, Grandma!
Hello, Ruko! Welcome home!
Just leave your bag on the floor there, it's cool.
pay off to me, everyone's face!
Okay, get off.
Hold on.
It's kinda high-claring stuff on that day.
Long time no see.
If you say so.
What's up, Grandma?
Yeah, just leave your bag on the floor there.
It's cool.
Well, that's that.
It's an apartment building after all.
Grandma wins this round.
Man, I thought it was going to be an office for sure.
Now I've got to clean the bathroom for a whole week.
Either way, one more pillar is all they need to finish the puzzle.
Puzzle? What do you mean?
Just think about how many points they'll get when they drop a pillar into that alley over there.
Oh.
They're only one building away from a Tetris.
And then the whole city might just disappear on us.
Finally!
Jeez, Grandma, these levels you make are getting way too hard for me.
Suppose I'd better start on dinner.
Oh, let me help you.
You've hardly been home for five minutes.
Why don't you relax a bit with your brother?
Or maybe you can get a start on bathroom cleaning duty.
Oh, no.
Nah.
I think I'd rather bother you.
Ew!
Would it kill you to take off your socks?
Now it stinks in here!
Yeah?
No!
You're going to give me the plague or something!
I want to go help with dinner!
It's always a party with Ayumu around.
Yeah, like the stinkiest party ever!
Come all the way out here just to hang with me?
You must really look up to your big bro.
No way!
I just came to get some milk tea.
Only one vending machine has my favorite.
Listen, try not to worry Grandma so much, okay?
I'm worrying her?
Yeah, a little.
She was telling me earlier that you haven't made any friends since you switched schools.
But it's not like I really need friends to be happy.
Well, you're not exactly shy, so I'm sure you'll meet someone.
But you know how Grandma can be.
She's always trying to look out for us.
Here.
What's that?
Just open it.
It's this card game a buddy from work told me about.
He said it's crazy popular with girls your age.
I don't know, I thought it might be fun.
Yeah, I think I've seen some girls in class playing this.
Well, there you go.
Perfect.
Now you have a secret weapon to make friends.
I didn't realize I was worrying Grandma so much.
See ya!
Was it chilly out there?
Cold, cold, cold, go away.
Warm, warm is here to stay.
I'm, uh...
I'm gonna go study.
Friends or no friends.
I don't want Grandma to worry about me all the time.
I guess it wouldn't hurt to give this a look at least.
Let's see here.
One of the cards is called an L-Rig and works as the player's avatar.
This one, maybe?
She's so cute!
Okay, so when it's the player's turn, this card will...
Hmm...
Oh, her voice is cute, too!
What?
Huh?
I heard a crash.
Oh no, are you hurt?
No, no, I'm okay.
Did you fall out of your chair?
Wait, you don't hear that voice?
What voice?
I know this isn't just in my head.
Uh, anyway, I'm fine.
You can go now.
I need to get back to studying, so, uh, why don't you take the first bath tonight?
Rue, wait.
But be careful.
Make sure the water's nice and warm.
Don't catch a cold, okay?
Fine, fine.
Good night.
You can't disappear!
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Bet you were the one giving me weird dreams.
What the heck are you, anyway?
Cards aren't supposed to talk.
Battle!
Battle?
So, you mean like a card battle thingy?
You don't need food, do you?
I mean, you're made of paper.
The broth would get you all wet and gross.
Battle!
Oh!
You still want to play, huh?
Do I just, like, ask them?
I wonder if they could hear you,
because I don't think the other girls' cards can talk.
I don't get this.
I found you!
Huh?
Um, hi?
I knew it!
You're a selector!
I don't know that word.
Aha!
Who's your Elrig?
Huh?
So I'm not crazy?
You can hear her voice, too?
Course I can!
Here, look.
I have an Elrig just like you.
Her name's Hario.
Now, on guard!
Yeah, I don't get this.
Perfect!
We've got the whole roof to ourselves!
Your card can speak, like real sentences,
but mine is kind of not quite there.
She, well, mostly just makes these little cat noises.
Ruko, right?
Kazuki, that is super cool.
You can hear all the Elrigs, too.
Huh?
I still don't get how that works.
Yeah, it's weird.
Only selectors can hear them.
But it's okay,
since Yuzuki fills me in on what Hanio is saying.
That word again.
Here, let me explain.
There are some players,
specially chosen ones,
who get to compete to become the Eternal Girl.
Wait.
Compete for what?
If you become the Eternal Girl,
your one true wish will be granted,
and you can make it happen just by winning enough battles.
Your wish will come true just like magic?
Well, that's what they say.
That's a bit of an oversimplification.
More precisely,
the Eternal Girl is someone with the power to make dreams come true.
If cards can talk,
then maybe anything could happen.
I admit it does sound like pure fantasy,
granting wishes and all that.
However,
these cards have the power without a doubt.
So long as you are able to triumph in battle,
you can make anything a reality.
That doesn't apply to all players, though.
Only selectors have living Elrigs like me.
You are different.
You are the chosen ones.
Perhaps you've noticed this yourself,
but several celebrities have announced
they're playing Wee Cross as well.
Since there's no easy way to find and identify other selectors,
it's possible they're trying to use the media
to draw out competitors.
Really?
There is one last thing you must know.
If you lose three battles,
you also lose your right to be a selector.
How is that?
The moment you lose your third battle,
we disappear.
Needless to say,
no wishes will be granted.
And even if you picked up the cards again,
your life would never be the same.
Cool story, Hanayo.
Thanks a bunch.
Now let's battle.
Wait, I...
I don't even have a wish yet.
Who cares?
You don't need one to battle.
We can still have fun.
Battle!
Battle now!
See?
Listen to your Elrig.
Come on, just one match.
Okay then.
What's the harm?
There you go.
Yuzuki,
don't pressure her into a match.
She hasn't even learned the rules yet.
I'm playing to win.
If she sucks at this,
it just makes things easier for me.
Open!
Where are we?
What happened?
How did you...
Battle!
Hold on.
Yuzuki, Hanayo!
Hell yeah.
And I get to go first.
Okay, Rugo,
it's your turn now.
That's nice,
but I still don't know how to play.
Can you hear me?
Kazuki!
The rules are pretty easy.
Just summon a signi,
call out the name of your Elrig,
then launch your attack.
Kazuki!
Cut it out!
Whose side are you on here anyway?
For the last time,
people on the outside can't hear you.
What's her name?
Oh,
I don't know.
Let's see.
Uh,
Tama?
Why Tama?
I know it's dumb,
but she's always meowing,
and I used to have a cat named Tama,
so...
Tama!
Here goes nothing.
Level one,
Gro!
Summoning a signi!
Tama attack!
Tama!
Ba-boom!
Was that bad?
I mean,
it's gone!
Did I break it or something?
Relax,
it's only a game.
As soon as the battle ends,
it'll be good as new.
It comes back?
Oh,
that's good.
Dang it, Kazuki!
This is all your fault!
If I don't win this,
I swear I'll pound your face in!
You can hear me,
right, Yuzuki?
I'm sorry,
but this is just wrong.
I want you to win,
but battles are supposed to be fair and square,
right?
If you have to do something underhanded
to make your wish come true,
will you really be happy in the end?
Level three,
Gro!
That's fun!
She's so happy.
Battle more!
Why?
If this is really her first battle,
why is she so strong?
If this keeps up, I...
Calm down, Yuzuki.
You can't give up after just one turn.
No, you're right, but...
Oh, get it together!
If you want your wish to come true,
and Kazuki to...
No!
I told you,
don't say that out loud!
Honey, yo,
come on!
Set up the game!
Hurry!
What are you kids doing?
Lunch break is over!
Get back to class,
or I'll write you up!
Yes, sir!
Wait, so now what happens?
Was the battle a win or a loss?
If an external influence terminates the battle,
losses are not counted.
We call it a no-gamer.
Good.
I was scared.
Yeah, so...
your wish?
Let's go, Kazuki!
Bye, I guess!
Okay.
That was weird.
What do you think?
Huh, Tama?
Oh, she's been out cold
since the battle ended.
She really is super cute,
isn't she?
Well, most of the time.
They use up all of their power
in battle.
When it's over,
they usually just sleep.
Hanayo's the same.
Oh, I see.
So, uh...
Kazuki's not with you anymore?
Just because we're twins
doesn't mean we're connected
at the hip.
Listen,
could you not tell anyone
about what Hanayo said earlier?
Said about what?
You trying to make fun of me?
I really don't know
what you mean!
Hey, uh...
If you're not too busy,
you wanna...
hang out?
Oh, Ru, you're home.
And you brought a friend.
Hi, nice to meet you.
You don't mind
if we hang out here, do you?
Of course not.
In fact,
I need to step out for a bit.
Help yourself to rice crackers.
Huh?
Well, don't I feel dumb?
It's funny.
Oh, I thought you must have
heard what she said for sure.
No, I don't think I did.
Oh, I was flipping out
over nothing.
Totally.
I'm guessing it was your wish,
Hanayo said.
Sorry, being nosy.
Yeah.
It's something I want
to come true no matter what.
But it's not the kind of wish
someone can make happen,
like with a bunch of hard work
or whatever.
That's all I'll say.
I understand.
I had given up, of course.
But when I met Hanayo
and became a selector,
she told me that even miracles
aren't beyond my reach.
And I want to believe her.
I want to believe that I can win
and become the Eternal Girl.
To have the power
to make my wish come true.
And all you have to do
is win, huh?
Well, okay then.
Let's have a card battle.
Only this time,
I'll lose on purpose, cool?
I'm not interested
in this Eternal Girl thing anyways.
No thanks.
I'll pass.
If Kalsuki ends up hating me,
then there's no point.
It defeats the purpose of my wish.
Hmm?
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Tea time, ladies!
Back already?
Rice crackers are a sorry snack
for you girls,
so I picked up something
a little more tasty.
Ooh, treats!
Wow, cake and macarons
and Bavarian cream?
Grandma, this is nuts!
There's no way
we can get all of this.
Thanks a bunch!
Oh my gosh, it's so good!
All of it is just amazing!
Glad to hear it.
Why didn't you tell me
you had such a nice friend, Ru?
Now I'm all recharged.
See you later!
Yeah, see ya!
I don't know too much
about Wee Cross yet,
and to be honest,
it all seems kind of scary.
But it's thanks to you,
Grandma so happy.
I'm glad I met you.
Ru Han, dinner's ready!
Coming!
Oh, I, uh, wanted to show you something.
What's that?
Actually, Yuzuki wasn't the only friend
I made today.
There's one more.
Her name's Tama.
時計時影の影に
うなずいたら
終わりのボアが
開き始まる闇
危うい答え
そこに見え隠れる
今日の祈りは
明日
多分になる
天と地を映す
逆さまの迷路
回り出した
歯車
人混みの中で
耳を澄ましたら
魂を招く
あの鈴の音
響く空へ
無限の果てまでは
進むしかない
自分で選んだ
未来だから
届かない今すぐも
揺れる太陽を
いつか取り戻す
笑顔の場所